this problem
asks us to use the array each method
to print the plural of each word in our
string
words you can see that string on line
one
we have four words in our string each
separated by a space
because this problem asks us to use
array each
we know we want to split this string
into an array
since each word in this string is
separated by a space
we can simply call split
on our string and pass in the space
character
as the pattern we want to split the
string on
let's pass the returned array as an
argument to put s
and take a look at our output
the output we see already looks pretty
similar to the expected output provided
by the problem
however we're missing one important
detail here
we need to output the plural form of
these words
and for each of these words that simply
involves adding an
s on to the end of the word so let's go
back to our code
the problem tells us to use array each
and we can use that on the array that
was returned
by invoking the split method
so we'll simply chain the array each
method
onto our split invocation
to iterate through that returned array
let's call our block parameter word
now we need to think about what code we
want to put in this block
what do we want to do with each word
well we know we want to output each word
so let's invoke put us and password in
as the argument
and run our code and we expect the
output to
be the same as what we saw previously
and it is we're still printing each
element of this array
so on line four of our code let's use
concatenation
to add an s onto the end of each word
when we pass it in as an argument to put
s
now we expect to output the result of
appending an s
to the word and that should give us the
plural form of
each word
and it does
[Music]
you